{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How old are you?",
      "answer": "45",
      "type": "text",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "Please state your gender.",
      "answer": "Man",
      "type": "radio",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you live in any of the following urban areas?",
      "answer": "Greater Sydney area",
      "type": "radio",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "Which car brands have you seen or heard advertising ELECTRIC CARS lately?",
      "answer": "Tesla, Hyundai, Nissan, Ford",
      "type": "text",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "If you were to buy an ELECTRIC CAR today, which brand would be your first choice?",
      "answer": "Tesla",
      "type": "text",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "Which other ELECTRIC CAR brands would you consider?",
      "answer": "Tesla, Nissan, Hyundai, Kia",
      "type": "text",
      "confidence": 0.85
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the below brands' ELECTRIC CARS have you heard of?",
      "answer": "Tesla",
      "type": "checkbox",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the below brands have you seen or heard advertising ELECTRIC CARS lately?",
      "answer": "None",
      "type": "checkbox",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you have access to a car in your household (also via sharing services, car pool etc)?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "type": "radio",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you have an electric or electric hybrid car within your household?",
      "answer": "No",
      "type": "checkbox",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "If you were to buy a car today, what type of car would you most likely choose?",
      "answer": "Petrol engine car",
      "type": "radio",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "If you were to buy a car today, how likely would you be to buy an ELECTRIC CAR?",
      "answer": "Likely",
      "type": "radio",
      "confidence": 0.9
    },
    {
      "question": "What is your personal total income before tax per year?",
      "answer": "$100 001 - $120 000",
      "type": "radio",
      "confidence": 0.9
    }
  ],
  "topic": "Social Topics",
  "points": 0,
  "platform": "myopinions",
  "timestamp": "2025-08-19T03:00:03.599109"
}